

MASTER'S STUDENT IN DATA ANALYSIS, CYBERSECURITY AND CLOUD COMPUTING

I am a computer engineer based in Andoain, specializing in designing unique solutions that integrate development, research, and visual representation. With a passion for problem-solving and a keen interest in the latest technological innovations, I bring a multidisciplinary approach to challenges, blending technical expertise with a creative mindset.

SKILLS

- Programming languages Python, JavaScript, Java, C
- **Development** CI/CD, Unit Testing, Microservices
- Architecture Cloud Computing, Microservices, Distributed Systems
- Fields of study Machine Learning, Cybersecurity, DevOps

EXPERIENCE

Edertek | System Administrator Internship

Arrasate, Spain | 09.2020 - Present

- Supported the activities of the organization in terms of machine virtualization and software installation activities
- Managed a VMware cluster, dealt with user tickets and took part in decision making within the IT department
- Enabled the organization to internalize IT operations expertise and standardize practices

Edertek | Final Degree Project

Arrasate, Spain | 11.2021 – 07.2023

- Aided the organization with the certification of the ISO 27001 security management standard
- Designed and partially implemented a plan for the standard
- Developed 12 new policies and procedures, as well as reviewing and improving 14 existing policies and procedures to ensure compliance

EDUCATION

Mondragon Uniberstsitatea

Master's Degree in Data Analysis, Cybersecurity and Cloud Computing

Arrasate, Spain | 09.2022 - Present

Mondragon Uniberstsitatea

Degree in Computer Engineering

Arrasate, Spain | 09.2018 - 06.2022

CERTIFICATES

Cambridge Assesment English (CAE)

C1 Advanced 04/09/2018

Eusko Jaurlaritza

B2 Euskara 29/05/2018